<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Arduino-mkr-nb-1500s on Managed IoT Cloud Workshops</title>
    <link>https://pwntus.github.io/mic-workshops/arduino-mkr-nb-1500/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Arduino-mkr-nb-1500s on Managed IoT Cloud Workshops</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://pwntus.github.io/mic-workshops/arduino-mkr-nb-1500/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Arduino MKR NB 1500</title>
      <link>https://pwntus.github.io/mic-workshops/arduino-mkr-nb-1500/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pwntus.github.io/mic-workshops/arduino-mkr-nb-1500/</guid>
      <description>The Arduino MKR NB 1500 comes fully compatible with Narrow Band IoT NB classes and LTE CAT M1 networks. In this workshop we&amp;rsquo;ll go through how to provision a device in MIC and how to program the Arduino MKR NB 1500 to send data using the open telenor.iot APN over the Telenor NB-IoT network.
Before continuing, make sure that:
 You have a valid MIC account: https://startiot.mic.telenorconnexion.com/signup You are able to login to the MIC App Board: https://startiot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Provision a Device</title>
      <link>https://pwntus.github.io/mic-workshops/arduino-mkr-nb-1500/provision/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pwntus.github.io/mic-workshops/arduino-mkr-nb-1500/provision/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ll start by provision a device, called a Thing in MIC, which will represent our device in the physical world.
Create a new Thing Type To do so, login to the App Board and click on the NEW THING TYPE button in the top left corner:
Give your Thing Type a Label, Description and a Domain and click SAVE.
Create a new Thing Click on your new Thing Type that has appeared in the list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup Arduino IDE</title>
      <link>https://pwntus.github.io/mic-workshops/arduino-mkr-nb-1500/arduino-ide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pwntus.github.io/mic-workshops/arduino-mkr-nb-1500/arduino-ide/</guid>
      <description>Next we&amp;rsquo;ll setup the Arduino IDE to work with the Arduino MKR NB 1500 board.
Download the latest Arduino IDE version for your platform and install.
Add Board Support  Open Arduino IDE and go to Tools ⟶ Board ⟶ Boards Manager. Search for and install Arduino SAMD (32-bits ARM Cortex-M0+) Boards. Close the IDE.  Install Pre-Release Core In order to install the pre-release core, you need to decompress the supplied ArduinoCore-samd-newboards.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>